You should have an avatar, a person
that you want to help.
This is actually where a lot of people
that I work with make massive mistakes.
They think they want to help nurses get
fit, let's say.
I then tell them
that less than 1% of the world are nurses,
that most of them are
underpaid, fucking exhausted,
and looking to survive the week
and not get shredded
for a holiday to Cancun. I told
that person instead to focus on helping
exhausted
women regain control of their fitness
regimes.
Because let's be honest,
a mother of three children has many of the
same problems
as a nurse. Sleep, routine,
putting other people first.
It's important that we don't niche down
too far.
Instead of wanting to coach, I don't know,
CEOs to get fit, maybe aim for
high-functioning men and women,
because there may be a bricklayer who
wants to lose
15 kilograms before Christmas,
who's put a bet on with a tiler
that he works with
on site, and to him,
that could be worth whatever it is
that you charge.
It's essential you don't niche down too
far because you're just making your life
so
much harder.
So make sure each post resonates with
that audience, because if you
deliver 10 to 20 aha moments to someone,
they're going to start seeing you as
someone who understands their problems.
Now,
not everyone is going to want to hire you,
but maybe 5% to 10% of these
people are going to consider it.
So think about who it
is you want to work with.
Now write out their problems.
Now next to those, provide solutions via
content. Don't bunch these up either.
I hate it at the moment when people say,
"Here's five ways to have a better squat."
Like, shut up, you're not.
Just pick one and then blow my world away
with it
between 45 and 90 seconds.
Then you could do one piece of content
each for one
of those five principles, and boom,
that's nearly a week of content sorted.
As far as frequency, I think one a day
is a really good benchmark.
Number two, with every rep,
you will get better.
Every Olympian gold medalist once couldn't
do the thing they do.
They just got better at it to the point
that they're now world-class.
Even now,
you may think I'm some kind of
well-spoken, handsome geezer who
pronunciates and cleverly
and strategically plans his delivery of
these topics.
But the reality is I've just been doing
this a lot longer than you.
I've done more reps.
Same goes for jujitsu.
Most people I get beaten by have just done
it for longer than me.
So don't look for excuses.
It's not the market, it's not the economy,
it's the fact
you need to do more of this to get better
at this